**Dark**  **Light**

Search

Privacy Policy
==============

Who we are
----------

Our website address is: https://donbigs.com.

Comments
--------

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Media
-----

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

Cookies
-------

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Embedded content from other websites
------------------------------------

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

This privacy and policy applies to the site and all product and services offered by [DonBigs.com](https://www.donbigs.com/)

### Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including but limited to, when users visit our site, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection to other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site.  
Users may be asked for as appropriate, name, email address, Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site-related activities.

### Non-Personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about users when they interact with our site. The non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about user means of connection to our site such as the operating system, and the internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our site may use “cookies” to enhance user experience. User’s web browsers place cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are been sent. If they do so know that some of the sites may not function properly.

### How we use collected information

Donbigs.com may collect and use users information for the following purpose;

* To improve customer service  
    The information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and supports needs more efficiently.
* To send periodic emails  
    If the user decides to opt-in our mailing, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any period the user wants to unsubscribe from receiving future email, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each mail.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent user’s personal identification information to others. we may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification regarding visitors and our users with our business partner, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purpose outlined above.

### Changes to this privacy policy

[Donbigs](https://www.donbigs.com/) has the discretion to update this policy anytime when we do we will post a notification on the main page of our website, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. we encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect, you acknowledge to agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this site you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept this policy please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Search

Scholarship
===========

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/mtn-foundation-muson-music-scholarship-program/)

##### [MTNF/MUSON Music Scholars Programme 2022 for Nigerians](https://www.donbigs.com/mtn-foundation-muson-music-scholarship-program/)

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/world-bank-group-africa-fellowship-program/)

##### [World Bank Group Africa Fellowship Program 2022/2023 | Fully-funded to Washington, DC](https://www.donbigs.com/world-bank-group-africa-fellowship-program/)

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/grooming-university-grant/)

##### [Grooming Centre University Grant Scheme 2022 for Undergraduate & Postgraduate Students | 20 Million Naira](https://www.donbigs.com/grooming-university-grant/)

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/unilag-african-cluster-centre-postdoctoral-fellowship/)

##### [University of Lagos (UNILAG) African Cluster Centre (ACC) Postdoctoral Fellowship in African and Diaspora Studies 2022](https://www.donbigs.com/unilag-african-cluster-centre-postdoctoral-fellowship/)

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/mtn-scholarship/)

##### [MTN Scholarship Scheme 2022/2023](https://www.donbigs.com/mtn-scholarship/)

Recent Jobs
===========

JAMB News
=========

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/jamb-scraps-mop-up-utme/)

##### [Joint Admissions and Matriculation Board, JAMB Scraps Mop-up UTME, Insists on no Biometrics, no Examinations](https://www.donbigs.com/jamb-scraps-mop-up-utme/)

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/check-jamb-result/)

##### [JAMB RESULT 2022: How to Check JAMB Result Via Online/SMS](https://www.donbigs.com/check-jamb-result/)

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/jamb-mop-up-result-checking/)

##### [How to Check JAMB Mop-Up Result 2022](https://www.donbigs.com/jamb-mop-up-result-checking/)

[

](https://www.donbigs.com/print-original-jamb-result-slip/)

##### [How to Print Original JAMB Result Slip from 1978 till Date](https://www.donbigs.com/print-original-jamb-result-slip/)

Follow Us
=========

Copyright © DonBigs

[

](https://www.dmca.com/Protection/Status.aspx?ID=61bfac88-6e80-4c35-846a-83b614feb3e5 "DMCA.com Protection Status")
